A Guide to the Papers of Norborne Berkeley 1918-1964
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: General Correspondence 1918-1964
  - Personal Correspondence, Taxes - State 1950-1954 (Box 50)
  - Personal Correspondence, Trinity Episcopal Church 1950-1954 (Box 50)
  - Personal Correspondence, U 1950-1954 (Box 50)
  - Personal Correspondence, University Club 1950-1954 (Box 50)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia 1950-1954 (Box 50)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, University of Virginia Alderman Fund 1950-1954 (Box 51)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Law School 1950-1954 (Box 51)
  - Personal Correspondence, V 1950-1954 (Box 51)
  - Personal Correspondence, Vacation in Europe 1954 (Box 51)
  - Personal Correspondence, W 1950-1954, 2 folders (Box 51)
  - Personal Correspondence, Water Conditioning 1950-1954 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, Y 1950-1954 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, Yale University 1950-1954 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, Z 1954 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, A 1955-1959 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, B 1955-1959 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, Berkeley General 1955-1959 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, Anne Churchill Berkeley 1955-1959 (Box 52)
  - Personal Correspondence, H. C. Berkeley 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence, Landon C. Berkeley 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence, Norborne Berkeley, Jr. 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence, Mrs. Norborne Berkeley, Jr. 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Club 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Steel Club 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Bethelehem Steel Co. 1955-1959, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Bethlehem Steel Co., Debentures 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Bethelehm Steel Co., Expense Account 1955-1959 (Box 53)
  - McDonald's Farm Hands n.d. (Box 53)
    Written for Bethlehem Steel Stockholders' meeting
  - Personal Correspondence, David M. Brush 1957-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence, Mrs. David M. Brush 1955-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence, C 1955-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence, Carlton House 1955-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence, Christmas Card List 1955-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence, City of Bethlehem Employer's Quarterly Income Tax 1955-1959 (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Contributions 1955-1958, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Contributions 1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, D 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Delta Kappa Epsilon 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Devon Yacht Club 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Directors as Stockholders (Outside Directors) 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, E 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School Board of Trustees 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School Upshur Fund 1955-1959 (Box 55)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School Minutes of Board Meetings 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, F 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, First National Bank and Trust Company of Bethlehem, Pennsylvania 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, Fuel Oil 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, Farmington Country Club 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, G 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, Georgica Association 1958-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, H 1955-1959 (Box 56)
  - Personal Correspondence, Robert T. Houk, III 1955-1956 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence, House "Stonesthrow" 1955-1959 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, House at Wainscott, L.I. 1958-1959 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence, House at New Caana (Kimberly Place) 1955-1959 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, House at Cincinnati, Ohio 1955-1957 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence, I 1955-1959 (Box 57)
  - Personal Correspondence, Insurance 1955-1959 (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, Insurance Receipts 1955-1959 (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, J- K- L 1955-1959, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, The Links Club 1955-1959 (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, M 1955-1959 (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, Maidstone Club 1955-1957 (Box 58)
  - Personal Correspondence, Maidstone Club 1958-1959 (Box 59)
  - Personal Correspondence, John Lindsay Moorehead 1955-1964, 2 folders (Box 59)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1955-1959 (Box 59)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, The Morgan Guaranty Survey 1959 (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, Nadler Suit 1955-1959 (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, N - O - P 1955-1959, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, Pine Valley Golf Club 1955-1957 (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, R 1955-1959 (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, M. E. Randolph Fiftieth Birthday 1955 (Box 60)
  - Personal Correspondence, S 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Saucon Valley Country Club 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, Saucon Valley Country Club Receipts 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, Stock Purchases, Sales 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, T 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, Tax Receipts 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, Trinity Episcopal Church 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, U 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, University Club 1955-1959 (Box 61)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Alumni Association 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, University of Virginia Alumni Association Publications and Reports 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Law School 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Fortieth Reunion 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, V 1955-1959 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, Vacation 1955-1957 (Box 62)
  - Personal Correspondence, Vacation 1958-1959 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, W 1955-1959 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, Y - Z 1955-1959, 2 folders (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, A 1960-1962 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, B 1960-1962 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, Berkeley General 1960-1961 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, Anne C. Berkeley 1960-1961 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, H. C. Berkeley 1960-1961 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, Dorothea R. Berkeley 1960-1962 (Box 63)
  - Personal Correspondence, L. C. Berkeley 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Norborne Berkeley, Jr. 1960-1961 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Club 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Steel Club 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Steel Company 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Bethlehem Steel Company, Dividend Units 1961 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Bethlehem Steel Company Expense Accounts 1960-1961 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, David M. Brush 1960-1961 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Dorothea B. Brush 1960-1961 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, C 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Carlton House 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Christmas Lists 1960-1962 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence, Contributions 1960 (Box 64)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Contributions 1961-1962, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, City of Bethlehem Employer's Quarterly Earned Income Tax Return 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, Compensation for Directors 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, D 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, DKE 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, E 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School 1960-1962 (Box 65)
  - Personal Correspondence, Episcopal High School News 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, F 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, Farmington Country Club 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, First National Bank and Trust Company of Bethlehem, Pennsylvania 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, Fuel Oil 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, G 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, Georgica Association 1960-1962 (Box 66)
  - Personal Correspondence, H 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, House (Wainscott) 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, I 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, Insurance 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, Insurance Receipts 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, J - K - L 1960-1962, 3 folders (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, The Links Club 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, M 1960-1962 (Box 67)
  - Personal Correspondence, Maidstone Club 1960-1962 (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, Medical 1960-1962 (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. 1960-1962 (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, N - O - P 1960-1962, 3 folders (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, Private Party 1960-1961 (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, R 1960-1962 (Box 68)
  - Personal Correspondence, Retirement Letters 1961 Dec 31 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, S 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, Saucon Valley Country Club 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, Saucon Valley Country Club Receipts 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, T 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, Tax Receipts 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, Trinity Episcopal Church 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, University Club 1960-1962 (Box 69)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia 1960-1962, 3 folders (Box 70)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Law School 1960-1962 (Box 70)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia, The Raven Society 1957-1961 (Box 70)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Reunion of Class of 1916 1961 (Box 70)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Reactor 1961 (Box 70)
  - Personal Correspondence, V 1960-1962 (Box 71)
  - Personal Correspondence, Proposed European Trip of 1962 1961-1962 (Box 71)
  - Personal Correspondence, Vacations 1960-1962 (Box 71)
  - Personal Correspondence, W and Y 1960-1962, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Personal Correspondence and Papers, Quotations, Poems, Humor, etc. n.d. (Box 71)
  - Paper re. Registration of Cars 1937-1959 (Box 72)
  - Personal Correspondence, A 1963-1964 (Box 72)
  - Personal Correspondence, B 1963-1964 (Box 72)
  - Bear Lake Congress, Correspondence with other Members 1960-1963 (Box 72)
  - Berkeley Fund, Papers and Correspondence of Personal Trust 1956-1963 (Box 72)
  - Berkeley Family Geneology and History 1960-1964 (Box 72)
    Contains Correspondence and Charts
  - Berkeley Family Geneology and History 1920-1959 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence with Anne C. Berkeley 1962-1963 (Box 73)
  - Estate File of Dorothea Randolph Berkeley 1962-1963 (Box 73)
  - Landon C. Berkeley Correspondence 1962-1963 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence with Norborne Berkeley, Jr. 1962-1963 (Box 73)
  - Bethlehem Club of Bethlehem, Pennsylvania and Bethlehem Steel Club 1962-1964 (Box 73)
  - Bethlehem Steel Correspondence 1962-1964 (Box 73)
    Chiefly requests to and statements from the Real Estate Division
  - Bethlehem Steel, Stock Option Plan 1959-1961 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence with Mrs. D. M. Brush (formerly Mrs. R. T. Houk III) 1965-1964 (Box 73)
  - Correspondence with D. M. Brush 1962-1964 (Box 73)
  - C Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 73)
  - City of Bethlehem, Income Tax 1963 (Box 73)
  - D Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 73)
  - E Correspondence 1962-1964 (Box 73)
  - Episcopal High School 1963-1964 (Box 73)
  - F Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 73)
  - Farmington Country Club 1962-1964 (Box 73)
  - First National Bank of Bethlehem 1963-1964 (Box 74)
  - Articles and Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box 74)
    pertaining to the Dubious Origin of the Fourteenth Amendment and Desegregation of Schools
  - Fuel Oil, Apgar Oil Company 1963-1964 (Box 74)
  - G - H Correspondence 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Household Bill and Deed for House in Bethlehem 1962-1964 (Box 74)
  - Household Accounts and Property Definitions for Bethlehem House 1959-1962 (Box 74)
  - Transactions with New Jersey Zinc Company 1950-1963 (Box 74)
    Re: Bethlehem Property
  - Maidstone Club, L. I., New York 1963-1964 (Box 74)
  - House, Wainscott, Long Island 1962-1963 (Box 74)
  - Georgica Association, Wainscott, Long Island 1963 (Box 74)
  - Georgica Association, Pond Committee 1961-1963 (Box 74)
  - I Correspondence 1963-1964 (Box 74)
  - Insurance Receipts 1962-1964 (Box 74)
  - Insurance 1963-1964 (Box 74)
  - Personal Correspondence, Johns Hopkins Hospital and all of N. B.'s Medical Records 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, J - K - L 1963-1964, 3 folders (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, The Links Club 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, M 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, Maps 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, Membership and License Cards 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, Morgan Guaranty Trust Co. of New York 1963-1964 (Box 75)
  - Personal Correspondence, N - O 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, P 1962-1963 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, Portrait 1963-1964 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, Passports 1963 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, Parties, General 1963-1964 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, R - S 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, Saucon Valley Country Club 1963-1964 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, Saucon Valley Country Club Receipts 1963-1964 (Box 76)
  - Personal Papers, Social Security for maids 1964 (Box 76)
  - Personal Correspondence, T 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, Trinity Episcopal Church 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University Club 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, US Army 80th Division 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, US Government Bonds Records 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Law School 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Athletic Committee 1961-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia Law Day 1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, University of Virginia, Bobby Gooch Football Hall of Fame material 1959-1963 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, V 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, Vacation 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, W 1963-1964 (Box 77)
  - Personal Correspondence, Will 1952-1963 (Box 78)
  - Personal Correspondence, Old Wills of Norborne Berkeley and Dorothea R. Berkeley 1943-1963 (Box 78)
  - Personal Correspondence, Old Wills of Friends 1939-1961 (Box 78)
  - Personal Correspondence, X - Y - Z 1963, 3 folders (Box 78)
  - Application to The South Carolina Society of the Colonial Dames of America of M. E. Barnwell 1922 Feb. (Box 78)
  - Personal Correspondence, Anne Harrison Berkeley, First student at Wellesley 1947-1949 (Box 78)
  - Anne Poe Harrison Berkeleym Portrait n.d. (Box 78)
  - Portrait of Mary Nelson Berkeley at Barn Elms n.d. (Box 78)
  - Anne Poe Harrison Berkeley, Portrait hanging at Wellesley College n.d. (Box 78)
  - Dewberry, the Ancestoral Home of Anne Poe Harrison Berkeley n.d. (Box 78)
  - Anne Poe Harrison Berkeley at Wellesley n.d. (Box 78)
  - The Berkeley Silver Pitcher n.d. (Box 78)
- Series II: Papers of the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia 1949-1963
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors Minutes 1955-1959, 5 folders (Box 79)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors Minutes 1960-1982, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors 1963 (Box 80)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Board Docket 1956-1957 (Box 80)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Board Docket 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Budgets 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box 81)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Mary Washington College 1955-1962, 2 folders (Box 82)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Extension Division 1949-1961, 3 folders (Box 82)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Athletic Committee 1955-1961, 4 folders (Box 83)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Executive Committee 1957-1959 (Box 84)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Buildings and Grounds Committee 1955-1958 (Box 84)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Inauguration of Shannon 1960 (Box 84)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Finance Committee 1956 (Box 84)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Finance Committee 1957-1958, 2 folders (Box 85)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Annual Report and Summaries of Consolidated Endowment Fund 1961-1963 (Box 85)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Correspondence 1955-1957, 2 folders (Box 85)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Retiring Rector and Visitors Dinner 1960 Feb. 20 (Box 86)
  - University of Virginia Board of Visitors, Correspondence 1960-1962, 3 folders (Box 86)
  - University of Virginia, Selection of a New President Correspondence 1956 Nov. 12- 1959 Oct. 19, 2 folders (Box 87)
  - University of Virginia, Selection of a New President Correspondence 1956-1958 (Box 87)
- Series III: Business Papers 1916-1964
  - Subseries A: Bethlehem Steel Company 1916-1961
    - Memoranda of Law 1916-1917, 2 folders (Box 88)
      Re: Bethlehem Steel from Berkeley Work at Law Firm of Cravath and Henderson
    - Copies of Bethlehem Steel Agreements and Other Papers 1927-1929, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - Copies of Bethlehem Steel Agreements and Other Papers 1927-1929, 2 folders (Box 89)
    - Reports of Bethlehem Stock and Production 1935-1959 (Box 89)
    - Bethlehem Review Mailing List 1948-1961 (Box 89)
    - Biographical Information used in Nadler suit 1958 (Box 89)
    - Copies of Reports and Biographical material used in Nadler suit 1958 (Box 90)
    - Biographical material of Eugene G. Grace used in Nadler sui 1958 (Box 90)
    - Plans for Reorganization of Bethlehem Steel 1959 (Box 90)
    - Labor settlement of Steel Strike 1959-1960 (Box 90)
    - Bethlehem Steel Stockholders Information 1959-1960 (Box 90)
    - Operation Improvment for Bethlehem Steel 1960 (Box 90)
    - Notes on Speech at Retirement Party 1961 Jan. 12 (Box 90)
  - Subseries B: Oil and Gas Investments 1953-1964
    - Credits 1955-1958, 5 folders (Box 91)
    - Credits 1959-1961 June, 5 folders (Box 92)
    - Credits 1961 June-Aug. (Box 93)
    - Tax Statements 1953-1955, 3 folders (Box 93)
    - Statement made to United States Partnership Return of Income 1955 (Box 93)
    - Records (Expenditures) 1954-1955 (Box 93)
    - General 1953-1961, 3 folders (Box 94)
    - Selling of Gas and Oil Interests 1963 (Box 94)
    - Drilling Agreement Files n.d. (Box 95)
    - Drilling Agreement Files n.d. (Box 96)
    - Falcon Seaboard Drilling Company venture settlements 1953-1955 (Box 96)
    - F.A. Callery, Inc. venture settlements 1953-1959 (Box 96)
    - Account statements from Falcon Seaboard Drilling Co. 1956-1959 (Box 96)
    - Account statements from Falcon Seaboard Drilling Co. 1960-1962 (Box 97)
    - Tax statements for ventures 1962-1963 (Box 97)
    - Brauer Prospect, Logan County, Colorado 1954-1959 (Box 97)
    - Drilling Logs for Brauer #1 and U.P.R.R. Clearman Wells, Logan County, Colorado 1955 (Box 97)
    - Challis #1, Morgan Country, Colorado 1954 (Box 97)
    - Kiowa County, Kansas 1954-1956 May, 2 folders (Box 97)
    - Kiowa County, Kansas 1956 June-1959, 5 folders (Box 98)
    - Kiowa County, Kansas 1960-1964, 2 folders (Box 99)
    - Photostatic copies of Operating Agreements on Kiowa County, Kansas sites 1955 (Box 99)
    - Photostatic copies of Unit Operating Agreements of sites in Kiowa County, Kansas 1956 (Box 99)
    - Copies of Applications for Certificate of Public Convenience and Necessity for Kiowa County, Kansas 1956 (Box 99)
    - Contract for pipeline on sites in Kiowa County, Kansas 1956 (Box 99)
    - Contract for pipeline on sites in Kiowa County, Kansas 1956 Jan. 17 (Box 99)
    - Photostatic copies of Unit Opertaing Agreements and Leaseholds of sites in Kiowa County, Kansas 1957 (Box 99)
    - Agreement for Construction and Operations of Compressor Plant in Kiowa County, Kansas 1957-1958 (Box 99)
    - Unit Operating Agreement for site in Kiowa County, Kansas 1958 (Box 99)
    - Comanche County, Kansas 1964 (Box 100)
    - Drilling Reports for wells in Cheyenne County, Kansas 1955 Feb. 10 (Box 100)
    - Orville Glick Acreage, Harper and Sumner Counties, Kansas 1955-1959 (Box 100)
    - Orville Glick Acreage #2, Harper and Sumner Counties, Kansas 1959-1963 (Box 100)
    - Geological and Drilling reports in Sumner County, Kansas 1957 (Box 100)
    - Clark County Kansas 1954-1956 (Box 100)
    - Zweygardt #1, Cheyenne County, Kansas 1954-1955 (Box 100)
    - Gas Contract with Southern Natural Gas 1958 Nov. 21 (Box 101)
      Re: Little Bayou Pidgeon Prospect, Iberia Parish, Louisiana
    - Gas Contract with Hope Natural Gas Company 1958 Dec. 4 (Box 101)
    - Little Bayou Pidgeon Prospect, Iberia Parish, Louisiana 1954-1964, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Stella Prospect, Plaquemines County, Louisiana 1953-1964, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Gas Contract with United Pipe Line Co. with Contractual Agreements 1957 July 15 (Box 101)
      Re: Stella Field Plaquemines Parish, Louisiana
    - Industrial Gas Sales Contract with Oronite Chemical Co. 1957 Aug. 20 (Box 102)
      Re: Stella Field, Plaquemines, Parish, Louisiana
    - Scott Prospect, Lafayette Parish, Louisiana 1953-1962, 3 folders (Box 102)
    - Scott #5, Lafayette Parish, Louisiana 1955 (Box 102)
    - Samstown Prospect, Iberville Parish, Louisiana 1954 (Box 102)
    - Laurel Ridge Prospect, Iberville Parish, Louisiana 1953-1964, 2 folders (Box 102)
    - Donner Prospect, Terrebonne Parish, Louisiana 1953-1961 (Box 102)
    - River Aux Chenes Prospect, Plaquemines Parish, Louisiana 1953-1956 (Box 103)
    - Camardelle Prospect, St. Charles and Lafourche Parishes, Louisiana 1953-1957 (Box 103)
    - North Lafitte Prospect #1, Jefferson and Plaquemines Parishes, Louisiana 1953-1954 (Box 103)
    - North lafitte Prospect #2, Jefferson and Plaquemines Parishes, Louisiana 1953 (Box 103)
    - Kisatchie Forest Prospect, Winn and Grant Parishes, Louisiana 1943-1955 (Box 103)
    - Fallon Prospect, St. Charles Parich, Louisiana 1953-1954 (Box 103)
    - Northwest Crowley, Acadia Parish, Louisiana 1953-1955 (Box 103)
    - Burnside Prospect, Ascension and St. James Parishes, Louisiana 1953-1955 (Box 103)
    - Burly McCall Prospect, Ascension and Iberville Parishes, Louisiana 1954-1955 (Box 103)
    - Troth Well #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 103)
    - Reynolds #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 103)
    - Martin #1 1953-1954 (Box 103)
    - Cobble #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 103)
    - Dillon #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1955-1956 (Box 103)
    - Arnold #1, Lincoln County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 103)
    - Mabel Carr Prospect, Logan County, Oklahoma 1955-1961 (Box 103)
    - Drilling and Geological Reports on Cobble #1, Payne County, Oklahoma 1953 (Box 104)